kitchendreaming.com 2015-11-03

# Privacy Policy | Kitchen Dreaming

This privacy policy sets out how Kitchen Dreaming uses and protects any information that you give while using www.KitchenDreaming.com  Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Kitchen Dreaming may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from August 20, 2012.  
**  
What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * contact information including name and email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers and/or giveaways

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email or social media. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

  * A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
  * We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
  * Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

**Advertising**

  * Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers.
  * We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other click stream data.
  * The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Kitchen Dreaming disclaims all liability in connection therewith.
  * For information about opting out of Gourmet Ads and ad serving partners please visit; <http://www.gourmetads.com/about/privacy-policy>.
  * Finally, you can choose to disable or selectively turn off cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings.

**What Gourmet Ads May Collect  **

  * Aside from advertising, when transacting with Gourmet Ads websites (gourmetads.com, console.gourmetads.com, publishers.gourmetads.com advertise.gourmetads.com only) we may collect by means of contact form or application the following information: 
    1. contact information including email address and phone number
    2. demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests or other information relevant as required in regards to your enquiry or application for the purpose of commencing a commercial relationship with Gourmet Ads Pty Limited.

**Links to other websites**

  * Our website may contain links to other blogs and websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
  * We cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
  * You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**  
Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * If you have signed up to receive our newsletter and email updates, you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe option at the bottom of each email.
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us.
  * We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
  * If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us using our [contact form](http://kitchendreaming.com/aboutcontact.html).

**Use of our information here on KitchenDreaming.com**

  * You may not use any photograph, recipe, tutorial or text published on Kitchen Dreaming without express written permission. Pinning of posts and sharing posts via social media or linking back to posts is accepted and encouraged.
  * Please refrain from violating our copyrights and work by distributing, stealing, manipulating or editing my work without our permission. Legal action may be taken in the event you are found in breach of this policy.
  * This policy is effective August 20, 2012 and applied to any and all content published before this date and any and all content published hereafter.

**  
Giveaways and Competitions Policy**

We use Rafflecopter to administer our giveaways and competitions. This policy applies to all competitions and giveaways offered on Kitchen Dreaming:

NO PURCHASE NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN. A PURCHASE DOES NOT IMPROVE YOUR CHANCES OF WINNING. VOID WHERE PROHIBITED BY LAW.

1\.  Promotion Description: Please check custom terms & conditions for each giveaway or competition on the relevant Rafflecopter widget.  By participating in any Sweepstakes, each entrant unconditionally accepts and agrees to comply with and abide by the Official Rules and the decisions of Kitchen Dreaming (“Sponsor”), which shall be final and binding in all respects. Sponsor is responsible for the collection, submission or processing of Entries and the overall administration of the giveaway. Entrants should look solely to Sponsor with any questions, comments or problems related to the Sweepstakes.

2\.  Eligibility: Open to adults who are 18 years or older. Void where prohibited or restricted by law. Sponsor and their respective parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, distributors, retailers, sales representatives, advertising and promotion agencies and each of their respective officers, directors and employees (collectively, the “Promotion Entities”), and members of their immediate families and/or persons living in the same household as such persons, are ineligible to enter the Sweepstakes or win a prize.

3\.  Winner Selection: The winner of the Sweepstakes will be selected in a random drawing from among all eligible Entries received throughout the Promotion Period. The random drawing will be conducted by 48 hours by Sponsor or its designated representatives, whose decisions are final. Odds of winning will vary depending on the number of eligible Entries received. Winner will be notified by email at the email address provided in the Entry Information on or about 48 hours after the random drawing. Potential winner must accept a prize by email as directed by Sponsor within 48 hours of notification. Any winner notification not responded to or returned as undeliverable may result in prize forfeiture. The potential prize winner may be required to sign and return an affidavit of eligibility and release of liability, and a Publicity Release (collectively “the Prize Claim Documents”). No substitution or transfer of a prize is permitted except by Sponsor.

4\.  Prizes:  
Prizes and the number of prizes offered varies per giveaway or competition. Please check the relevant competition or giveaway for further details.

  * Only one prize per person and per household will be awarded. Gift cards and gift certificates are subject to the terms and conditions of the issuer. Prizes cannot be transferred, redeemed for cash or substituted by winner. Sponsor reserves the right in its sole and absolute discretion to award a substitute prize of equal or greater value if a prize described in these Official Rules is unavailable or cannot be awarded, in whole or in part, for any reason. The ARV of the prize represents Sponsor’s good faith determination. That determination is final and binding and cannot be appealed. If the actual value of the prize turns out to be less than the stated ARV, the difference will not be awarded in cash. Sponsor makes no representation or warranty concerning the appearance, safety or performance of any prize awarded. Restrictions, conditions, and limitations may apply. Sponsor will not replace any lost or stolen prize items.
  * Prize will only be awarded and/or delivered to addresses as given at time of acknowledgement of winning competition. All federal, state and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. Failure to comply with the Official Rules will result in forfeiture of the prize.

5\.  Online Entry: Enter the Sweepstakes during the Promotion Period online by signing into the entry form and perform the tasks provided. The entry form can be found on Kitchen Dreaming.

Automated or robotic Entries submitted by individuals or organizations will be disqualified. Internet entry must be made by the entrant. Any attempt by an entrant to obtain more than the stated number of Entries by using multiple/different email addresses, identities, registrations, logins or any other methods, including, but not limited to, commercial contest/sweepstakes subscription notification and/or entering services, will void that entrant’s Entries and that entrant may be disqualified. Final eligibility for the award of any prize is subject to eligibility verification as set forth below. All Entries must be posted by the end of the Promotion Period in order to participate. Sponsor’s database clock will be the official time keeper for this Sweepstakes.

6\.  Privacy: All entrants acknowledge that if they are chosen as a winner, certain of their personally identifying information may be disclosed to third parties at least as required by law, including, without limitation, on a winner’s list. All personal information submitted as part of the Sweepstakes may be shared by and between the Promotion Entities, and each of the Promotion Entities will use such information in accordance with their respective independent online privacy policies. The privacy policy of Kitchen Dreaming can be found at

7\.  Limitation of Liability: Sponsor is not responsible for any incorrect or inaccurate information, whether caused by website users or by any of the equipment or programming associated with or utilized in the Sweepstakes or by any technical or human error, which may occur in the processing of submissions in the Sweepstakes. Sponsor assumes no responsibility for any misdirected or lost mail, or any error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay of operation or transmission, communications line failure, theft or destruction or unauthorized access to, or alteration of entries. Sponsor is not responsible for any problems or technical malfunction of any telephone network or lines, computer online systems, servers or providers, computer equipment, software, failure of email or players on account of technical problems or traffic congestion on the Internet or at any website or combination thereof, including injury or damage to entrant’s or any other person’s computer related to or resulting from participating in or downloading materials in the Sweepstakes. If, for any reason, the Sweepstakes is not capable of running as planned, including infection by computer virus bugs, tampering, unauthorized intervention, fraud, technical failures, or any other causes beyond the control of Sponsor which corrupt or affect the administration, security, fairness, integrity or proper conduct of the Sweepstakes, then Sponsor reserves the right in its sole discretion to cancel, terminate, modify or suspend the Sweepstakes. In such event, Sponsor may, in its sole discretion, perform the random drawing from among all eligible Entries received prior to or after such cancellation, suspension, or modification.

In the event of a dispute concerning who registered online to participate in the Sweepstakes, the registration will be declared to have been made by the authorized account holder is defined as the natural person who is assigned to an email address by an internet provider, online service provider, or other organization (e.g., business, education institution, etc.) that is responsible for assigning email addresses for the domain associated with the submitted email address. A potential winner may be requested to provide Sponsor with proof that the potential winner is the authorized account holder of the email address. If a dispute cannot be resolved to Sponsor’s satisfaction, the entry will be deemed ineligible.

8\.  Winner’s List: To obtain a copy of any legally required winners list or a copy of the Official Rules, send the applicable request and a self-addressed, stamped, #10 envelope to Ronda Eagle cc: Kitchen Dreaming at Brickhope Lane, Goose Creek, SC. Request must be received no later than 6 MONTHS  after the official contest end date for the name of the winner and, by the end of the promotion, for a copy of the rules.

9\.  Sponsor: The Sweepstakes is sponsored by Kitchen Dreaming.com

10\. Rafflecopter Disclaimer: This promotion is powered by Rafflecopter. Metric Feat LLC (“Rafflecopter”) does not sponsor, administer or endorse this promotion. By entering this promotion, Participants agree to Rafflecopter’s Privacy Policy (http://www.rafflecopter.com/rafl/privacy/). For technical information about the Rafflecopter widget, please visit http://blog.rafflecopter.com/2012/08/anatomy-rafflecopter-giveaway/.

11\. Facebook Disclaimer: Entrants should understand that they are providing their information to the Sponsor and not to Facebook. This promotion is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with Facebook.

12\. Prize distribution: Sponsor cannot be held liable for any prizes that have not been distributed or that have arrived damaged or otherwise incorrect. It is the responsibility of the winner to liaise with the brand over any dispute regarding the sending of and receiving of the prize.

13\. By entering this giveaway, you are granting Sponsor the right to store your email address in a third-party email marketing system and email you periodically about Kitchen Dreaming. Sponsor will not share your details with anyone other than any other named Sponsors of this giveaway and the brands supporting it where applicable.
